The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Fellow cultivators,
how has my White Cloud Sect offended you ?
If you don't explain this,
you won't live another day !
If I use the restriction flag,
maybe I can take a few blows from these Soul Formation.
But I'm afraid it will be recognized in the future...
I'd rather avoid trouble.
I heard that the White Cloud Sect has Soul Formation cultivators,
I wish to challenge them all.
I hope you can forgive my intrusion.
Transform !
Middle stage Nascent Soul ?
You're overestimating yourself !
Clone !
Stop !
My teleportation
was cancelled ?
Don't dodge.
A Soul Formation's domain is hidden in his spells.
Experience it.
You are all so shameless.
You're shameless.
I'm shameless.
Did you ever look at yourself once ?
This energy cannot be blocked.
This is my Desperate Emotions Domain.
What is this ?
Not bad.
It was the right call to come here.
He abandonned happiness and anger, love and hatred.
He understood emotions, but gave up on feeling them.
Long live Lord Immortal !
This person is extremely ruthless.
To form this domain...
So heartless...
So lonely...
A domain...
So this is what a domain is !
I guess Senior came here
to allow your disciple to experience domains
in order to breakthrough to Soul Formation.
You, come out.
It's your turn.
Shi Qi\NWhite Cloud Sect Elder\NSoul Formation
Although Senior's cultivation is sky high,
that doesn't mean
that you can order our White Cloud Sect around !
You're all as stubborn as a cows.
You act exactly like your old Patriarch White Cloud.
Ancestral Spirit Token !
Since Senior has the Ancestral Spirit Token,
we Juniors must obey
but is Senior sure to want to use this token
to have all our Soul Formation cultivators
attack your disciple to help him experience domains ?
Cut the crap
and hurry up !
You, come out !
You have a good teacher.
If I had a chance to experience domains
back when I tried to reach Soul Formation,
I would have had a much smoother path.
Slowly experience this old woman's domain.
This is...
I'm sleepy...
I haven't been for so many years.
Wan'er...
Go to sleep,
you are so tired...
What
am I doing ?
If it weren't for the beads of killing intent,
I would have been completely lost in her domain.
A Middle stage Nascent Soul was able to resist my domain ?
It never happened before.
You, over there.
Come here.
Qing Song\NWhite Cloud Sect Elder\NSoul Formation
Your domain is quite special.
Once he experiences it,
we won't bother you anymore.
He cannot withstand
my domain.
Nonsense !
With me here,
even if your old Patriarch White Cloud were to come personally,
I would hold him off.
Time is accelerating ?
This is...
my spiritual energy is fading...
His domain can deplete all my spiritual energy and cause my body to age.
If it were to affect my life energy,
my life would be drained away.
My domain is
the passing of time.
Excellent !
What an amazing domain !
If you ever reach Ascendant,
your domain will be heaven defying !
You guys can keep this token.
Goodbye.
I'm getting old...
I can only teleport 100 000 li.
Senior,
what was that Ancestral Token ?
It's just a piece of junk.
I have many more.
It's one of my hobbies.
This is from the Heaven Escape Sect
This is from the Spirit Fog Sect.
This is from the Giant Demon Clan.
This is one is from a rank 5 country.
Wanna buy one ?
I can make a token of any sect for you.
Would you like a White Cloud Sect Leader token ?
Senior's technique is something Junior has never seen before.
I admire you.
You only know this one line ?
Forget it.
You've experienced some domains already.
You can keep the hat for now.
Now quickly reach Soul Formation and make wood carvings of me.
Seriously...
Domains...
Everything is a-changing.
Desperate love can turn into despair.
True happiness
turns one empty
and lazy.
But...
What's the passing of time ?
Uncle Wang !
I'm here to bring you wine.
Da Niu !
17 years later
Uncle Wang,
you are getting old, you should drink less.
It isn't good for your health.
Congratulations !
Thanks.
Come have a drink.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
The bride has so much dowry !
Come to my house for a drink !
Is the bride beautiful ?
She is !
This piece of land is good.
Thank you, Shopkeeper Wang.
Is this shop prosperous enough to pay the debt ?
Look at my chubby son !
Keep your voice down,
he finally fell asleep.
Mister Wang,
I will definitely pay the rent next month.
Shopkeeper Wang,
you have come !
Mister Wang,
come and taste my new orange.
If you don't pay the rent today,
then get to work.
Without realizing it,
I ended up owning most of the street as I lent money to more people.
All living beings
travel through heaven and earth.
Almost 20 years have passed.
What is the domain I am looking to form ?
What is the law of the heavens ?
After all these years,
I can neither see it
nor understand it.
Grandpa Wang !
Ceng Xiao Niu
Can I have a candy ?
I stole this wine for you.
Grandpa Wang,
does this wine taste good ?
I see you drinking it every day.
Uncle Wang !
You can't drink anymore today.
Okay...
Just one last sip.
I won't drink anymore today.
Da Niu,
how is your father ?
Same old illness.
Grandpa Wang,
you haven't told me
how the wine tastes.
It's not wine that Grandpa Wang drinks
it's Life.
I want to see where you can run off to.
Yi Fu\NWhite Cloud Sect Disciple\NFoundation Establishment
Mister Wang !
Save me...
What's the problem ? Tell me.
His Highness the Crown Prince...
I...
I thought he was looking for real backup
but it's just a mortal...
Since Xu Tao came to find you,
you two must have a close relationship.
You will also
be close together in death !
I don't want to bother with you.
You shouldn't attack me.
Go to hell.
My soul was damaged !
You...
You're not a mortal !
Master,
do you want me to...
I've been turning mortal for decades,
I won't ruin it for this.
Who is it ?
It's late already.
This...
Shopkeeper,
please find two pairs of hands
to help me carry this man into my shop.
Shopkeeper Wang,
I think we should report this incident.
Otherwise, you'll be in trouble.
It's fine.
He's a good person.
Shopkeeper Wang really is a good person.
Second son, sixth son,
come out !
Help me to carry this man
into Shopkeeper Wang's house.
Sure.
If I don't intervene,
I'm afraid he won't survive.
Master !
I need to see Master !
Junior !
Hurry !
Why are you so badly injured ?
I need to see Master.
How could a mortal cause such injuries ?
Master ! Master !
Fu'er...
What's wrong ?
Master !
Zhou Wutai\NWhite Cloud Sect Elder\NPeak Late stage Nascent Soul
I've had my share of wounds,
now I want to fight back.
Is my destiny a wall of restrictions
that's blocking all my hopes
for life ?
My flesh and blood witnessed the past,
my adversity pushed me to brave the waves.
How do you navigate through the years passing by ?
Nirvana and rebirth are no longer
out of reach.
Immortals
are obsessed with delusions of grandeur.
Renegades
seek to crush the impermanence of the heavens.
Don't tell me that I overestimate myself
and that the path to revenge leads to hell
because I don't see the harm in that.
My new body opens its eyes
and awakens from its dream.
I have overcome many trials
to get this body back.
No matter how many endless dark nights go by,
I can still see.
By sticking to this thought, I will get it done
by my own hands.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,
I need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,
only my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.